wikijob.co.uk 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | WikiJob Graduate Jobs

## Information we store and use

When you register with us or order from us, we ask for personal information such as your name, e-mail address, employer details, contact telephone number and so on. All this is necessary to verify your identity and eligibility for the services provided by WikiJob. You may also be asked for additional information if you sign up to receive news updates or other information services or to enter into competitions.

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, PayPal.  You can review the PayPal privacy policy at [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/ "www.paypal.com").  We will share information with PayPal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.

We do not store your financial information.

## Information safety and security

We also operate security procedures as required under UK data protection legislation (the Data Protection Act 1998) to protect the information that we store about you from unauthorised access.

## Internal confidentiality

WikiJob aims to protect your privacy in the following ways:

  * Access to account information is limited to those who need access for the performance of their job.
  * We use full login and password controls on our data access systems.
  * All full and part-time employees are required to sign a confidentiality clause as part of their terms of employment.
  * Confidentiality and database access controls are reviewed periodically and updated as required to further protect your personal data.

## Use of ‘cookies’ and recording information

This site uses cookies, but they do not contain any personal information about you and are used only to determine your browser and user preferences for our site. This helps us to provide you with a tailored service and to improve your browsing experience. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser software to not accept cookies. You should still be able to use the majority of our site without cookies enabled, but certain features may not be available without cookies.

We may also feature advertising delivered from third party servers, which may also seek to set cookies. Such businesses have their own privacy policies which we can supply upon request. We do not deal with any advertising sales houses unless they confirm that cookies they use do not record personal information.

We record IP addresses of all people visiting our site. We do not use this information for tracking the activities of specific visitors to the site under normal operational conditions, but we may use this information in connection with any misuse of our site or any attempt to access our site or its data without authorisation.

Certain parts of our site permit users to input information or comments. We will retain copies of any such data.

## Consent

All the information we collect via our website or through correspondence with you may be used for the following purposes by WikiJob or any legal entity connected with it:

Unless we are legally required to do so, we will not pass your personal information to an unconnected third party without your consent save where it is necessary for the purposes of crime prevention or prosecution or in connection with litigation.

## Changes

The manner in which we collect or utilise data may change over time, and this policy may also change.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this site so that you may ensure that you are fully informed of your rights and can notify us of any changes to your preferences.

## Your rights

If for any reason, you are unsure about the personal and account information we are holding in your name, please contact us. We can review your file and update the records if required. You can contact our customer service team by email, phone or fax, all as listed in the ‘contact us’ section of the WikiJob website.

Anyone whose personal information is stored by us has certain rights under UK data protection legislation. If you wish to exercise any of those rights, please write to:

The Data Controller, 85 Clerkenwell Road, London, EC1R 5AR

  * Dealing with transactions and account queries
  * Research
  * Processing payments, credit reference checking & fraud detection
  * To identify whether any offers from us or our partners may be suitable for you (but of course you will not receive any offers if you tell us that you do not wish to receive them);
  * For crime prevention or in connection with litigation.
